This kitty is Mittens,
this one is Fitzhugh
and this little guy
in the cat condo is Jinkies.
Yep, that's a lot
of cats, Jo Lynn.
Single, are you?
( phone ringing )
Chandler Bing.
JOEY:
Hey.
How come you're answering
your own phone?
Where's your crazy assistant?
What's up, Joe?
Okay, what have we always
wanted to do together?
Braid each other's hair
and ride horseback on the beach?
No, no, no.
When you get home tomorrow night
you and I are going to be
at the Wizards-Knicks game...
courtside!
Courtside? Oh, my God.
Yeah, maybe Michael Jordan
will dive for the ball
and break my jaw with his knee.
That is so cool.
I'll let Monica know.
( phone ringing )
Hello?
Joey just called.
He's got
courtside Knicks tickets
for him and me tomorrow night.
Really?
But tomorrow night's
the only night
I get off from the restaurant.
If you go to the game
then we won't have a night
together for another week.
But hey, it's courtside.
The cheerleaders
are going to be right in fr...
That's not
the way to convince you.
Chandler, look.
I don't want to be
one of those wives that says
"You can't go to the game.
You have to spend time with me."
So if you could just realize it
on your own...
I-I know, you're right.
I want to see you, too.
I just got to figure out a way
to tell Joey, you know?
He's really
looking forward to this.
Tell him that you haven't
seen your wife in a long time.
Tell him that having
a long-distance relationship
is really difficult.
Tell him that what little time
we have together is precious.
Eh, eh...
I'll think of something.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Wow.
Wow, you look, uh...
I mean, it's just, uh....
That, that dress, uh...
Well I hope the ends of
these sentences are good.
Well, they're good.
It's just been a while since
I've seen you like this.
You, you clean up good.
Oh, well...
well thank you.
Okay, stop. Stop looking
at me like that.
Last time that happened,
that happened.
Oh, right, right.
So, are you, uh...
You excited about your,
your first night away from Emma?
Yeah, yeah.
Phoebe and I are going
to have so much fun.
And thank you for watching
the baby, by the way.
Oh, it's fine.
Actually, I invited Mike over.
Phoebe's Mike?
Yeah.
I didn't know
that you guys hung out.
We don't
but I thought it'd be nice
to get to know him.
You know, maybe have
a little dinner
drinks, conversation.
Oh, that's so cute.
Ross and Mike's first date.
Is that
going to be awkward?
I mean, what are you guys
going to talk about?
I don't know.
But, you know, we have
a lot in common, you know?
Um, he plays piano,
I played keyboards in college.
He's been divorced, I have
some experience in that area.
( knocking at door )
Yeah.
Hi.
Hey.
Ooh, girls'
night out, indeed.
Okay, so now, I think Emma
is probably down
for the night
but if you need
anything, Ross...
Rach, Rach, we'll be
fine, all right?
You go have fun.
Okay, you, too.
And I hope you score.
Bye.
So...
Welcome.
I got beer.
I got bottled breast milk.
Eh, why don't we start
with the beer.
Okay.
So, um, Phoebe tells me
you, uh, you play piano.
Yeah.
You know, I used to play
keyboards in college.
Oh, do you have one here?
No.
Okay.
( chuckles )
Um, you know, I'm divorced.
Uh, Phoebe, Phoebe says
that you've been divorced?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I don't
I don't really like
to talk about it.
That's okay, we'll talk
about something else.
So you're
a paleontologist, right?
Yeah.
My cousin's
a paleontologist.
Ah.
Well, he and I would probably
have a lot to talk about.
Hi.
Hey.
Welcome home.
Oh, well, look at you.
Yeah, what
do you think?
Well, it's great.
It's just...
well, I'm wearing the same
thing underneath, so...
See what I...
( thudding and grunting )
JOEY:
Hey?! How come
your door's locked?
Just a second.
No, no, no, no, no.
Joey can't know
that I'm here.
Why not?
Because I didn't know
how to tell him
I couldn't go
to the Knicks game
so I told him
I had to stay in Tulsa.
So you lied to him?
It's always better to lie
than to have
the complicated discussion.
Except with you.
Hey, open
the door!
What's going on?
( knocking )
What are you...
Why are you
dressed like that?
Oh, because, um...
well, Chandler's going to be
home in a couple of days
so I thought I would just,
uh, you know
practice the art
of seduction.
Oh, I thought I heard
a man's voice before.
No, I was just doing Chandler's
side of the conversation.
You know, like,
"Hi, how do I look?"
( deeper ):
"Really sexy.
Could I be any more
turned on?"
Okay... whoa, whoa.
Why are there two
glasses of wine out?
Because one of them
is for you.
Cheers.
Okay, bye-bye.
You know, it's funny.
I've been, uh, practicing
the art of seduction myself.
Hi-ya...
You might want
to keep practicing.
( cell phone ringing )
It's Joey.
What?
Hey, Joe.
Dude, come home.
What? Why?
Come... home.
Look, I can't.
What's going on?
I don't know how
to tell you this, but, uh...
I think Monica's
cheating on you.
I told you
you shouldn't have married
someone so much hotter than you.
All right, look.
If you can't come home and deal
with this, then I'm gonna.
No!
I just heard him.
Can you... hear him... now?
No.
All right, I'm going in.
No, wait!
I heard him again.
All right, look.
Just stay there.
I'm coming home.
Okay, great.
I'll see you when you get here.
I'm going to wait
out in the hall
in case the dude comes out.
Is that really necessary?
Absolutely.
You'll do it for me.
Not that you ever have to
because I know how
to keep my women satisfied.
( blowing note )
Shouldn't the pizza
be here by now?
I mean, they said
30 minutes or less.
How long has it been?
Eleven minutes.
And now 12.
So, you like the beer?
I do, I do.
Although it's actually
a lager.
Oh.
What's the difference
between beer and lager?
I don't know.
We could look it up.
Things are about to get wild.
Oh, God, remember the girls'
nights we used to have?
Sitting around talking
about you and Ross?
Oh, God, that seems like
forever ago.
I know.
Oh...
So what's going on
with you and Ross?
Well, um, I don't know.
I mean, for a long time,
nothing.
But you know, actually,
right before you picked me up
Ross and I had a, uh,
little thing.
Oh, my God, I love things.
What happened?
Well, um, first he told me
he liked how I looked
and, uh, then we had
a little, um...
eye contact.
Eye contact?
Mm-hmm.
I hope
you were using protection.
MAN:
Excuse me, um...
these are from
the two gentleman
at the end
of the bar.
Oh, should we send them
something back?
Ooh, let's do.
Let's send them
mashed potatoes.
No, wait, don't do that.
Then that's going to make them
think they can come over here.
So, what if they do?
Well, we're not here
to meet guys.
You have a boyfriend,
I have a...
baby and a Ross.
Yeah, but...
nothing has to happen.
We're just having fun.
You know, not everything has
to go as far as "eye contact."
Chandler, you have
to tell Joey
that you're not
in Tulsa.
Don't you think
it's better for him to think
that you're cheating on me
than for him to think
that I'm cheating on him?
I heard it.
I don't want him to think
that I'm having an affair.
All right, I've got a plan.
I'll go down the fire escape...
Yes, because
all good plans start with
"I'll go down the fire escape."
Hear me out, woman!
I'll go down the fire escape,
then I'll wait for a while.
Then when I come up the stairs
it'll be like I just
got back from Tulsa.
Then Joey and I will come in
and see that
there's no guy in here.
Aren't you afraid that Joey's
going to figure all this out?
I heard it.
I'm just going to wait
for a little while.
Scary pigeon's back?
It's huge.
( making lip
flapping noises )
( noises continue )
( lip flapping noises )
Oh, my God, I can't
believe you live
in that building.
My grandmother
lives in that building.
Ida Green?
No sense of personal space.
Kind of smells like chicken.
Looks like a potato.
"Spuds"
is your grandmother?
That's my bubby!
( both chuckling )
So, we're on our way
to a couple of parties.
Um, maybe
we could get your numbers
and give you guys a call
if we find something fun.
Yeah. I'm sorry,
we weren't really looking
for anything to happen
with you guys.
I... I have a boyfriend.
All right.
It's no big deal.
So, she has
a boyfriend.
And what
is your situation?
Oh, well, it's complicated.
I don't actually have
a boyfriend, but, uh...
Then can I have
your number?
I'm sorry, no.
Okay.
Oh, sure.
Oh, my God, you're giving
your real number.
Okay, thanks.
I'll give you a call
later tonight.
Great.
Bye.
Wow. So, that's great.
You, Bill, Ross and Emma
are going
to be so happy together.
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
He was cute and he liked me.
It was an impulse.
What about Ross?
What about your moment?
Don't you want to talk
to Ross about it?
No, no, 'cause I know exactly
how the conversation's
going to go.
"Hey, Ross, you know, I think
we had a moment before."
"Yeah...
( clearing throat ):
me, too."
"Well, but I'm not sure I really
want to do anything about it."
"Yeah.
( clearing throat ):
Me neither."
( clearing throat )
"Well, should we just continue
to live together
and not really tell each other
how we're really feeling?"
"Yeah, that works for me."
( clearing throat )
Yeah, I see what you mean.
By the way, nice
Ross imitation.
Oh, thanks.
But your Rachel
wasn't whiny enough.
Wha... hey!
Better.
Well, the point is
maybe I should just stop
waiting around
for moments with Ross, you know?
I should just move on
with my life.
So, really?
You're moving on from Ross?
I don't know.
Do I have to decide right now?
Well, you kind
of just did.
That guy's going
to call you tonight.
Ross is going to
pick up the phone
and that's a pretty
clear message.
Oh, my God-- Ross.
Ross is going
to pick up the phone.
Oh, I have to get
my number back.
Oh, my God, he's gone.
"Oh, I have to get
my number back.
Oh, my God, he's gone."
Dead on.
( sighing softly )
( air whooshing out )
You know, I'm going to take off.
So soon?
Well, yeah.
Okay. Well, thanks, uh,
thanks for the beer.
You mean lager.
Ah, yeah.
Good times.
( groaning )
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Hey, Mike, it's me.
Listen,
is Ross near you?
Uh, no, I just left.
Well, you have to go back in.
Wha... go back?
To "the land
where time stands still?"
I'm so sorry, honey, but, okay,
Rachel gave this guy her number
and, um, she doesn't want Ross
to answer the phone
so, you have to intercept
all his calls.
I can't do that.
He says
he can't do that.
Oh, give me...
Hi, Mike.
Hi, listen, I know
that this is a lot to ask
but you know what?
If you do this, I...
Phoebe will do
anything you want.
Seriously,
I'm talking dirty stuff.
All right.
Thank you.
Hello? Hi.
I'm sorry about her.
But she wasn't wrong
about the dirty stuff.
All right, I'll do it.
But, really
how much dirtier can it get?
( chuckling ):
Oh, Mike...
Bye.
( knock at door )
Hey, buddy.
Uh... hi.
Um
can I come back in?
Why?
Well, I, I was just thinking
about how much more
we have to talk about.
But you left.
Wow, that
didn't take long.
I thought you said Tulsa
was a three-hour flight.
Well, you're forgetting
about the time difference.
( gasping ):
Chandler, you're home!
That's right.
Your husband's home,
so now the sex can stop.
What are you saying?
Joey said that
you're in here
with another man.
There's no man in here.
How dare you
accuse me of that?
( gasping )
All right, all right,
then maybe you won't mind
if me and my friend
take a look around, huh?
Mwa-ha-ha!
( thumping noises )
What's he doing?
I arranged some pillows on
the bed to look like a guy.
Bedroom's clear.
Although you might need
some new pillows.
All right, well,
I'll check the guest room.
( sniffing )
Why do I smell men's cologne?
I think that's you.
( sniffing )
Oh, yeah, I rubbed a magazine
on myself earlier.
There's nobody
here, Joe.
I guess not.
I can't believe
you thought I was cheating.
You owe me an apology.
Yeah, right,
Monica, I'm so sorry.
It's an honest mistake.
It could happen to anybody.
All right, see ya.
Whoa, whoa,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
If you just got back
from Tulsa
how did your suitcase
beat you here?
I climbed down the fire escape
and you can't put that
in the closet?
So, with the exception
of the fermentation process
beer and ale
are basically the same thing.
Fascinating, isn't it?
Maybe you should look
up "fascinating."
( phone ringing )
I'll get it.
Hello, Ross's place.
Mike speaking.
It's for you.
I don't understand
what just happened here.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I, I told you I was in Tulsa
because I wanted to spend
the night with Monica
and I, I didn't know,
I didn't think you'd understand.
What, you think
I'm too dumb to understand
that a husband
needs to be with his wife, huh?
You think I'm, like, "Duh!"
Joey.
Yeah?
I don't know what to say.
We shouldn't
have lied to you.
Yeah, I feel so bad.
Is there anything I can do
to make it up to you?
Yeah, you could go
to the game with me.
Even though I know
you said you couldn't.
But then you lied to me
and tricked me
and gave me a bump on the head.
I'm sorry, that's the one thing
I can't do.
I promised
I'd be with Monica.
All right.
You can go.
What?
You should go to the game.
It's okay; I want you to.
Really?
You going to be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
You know, maybe
I'll stay here
and practice the
art of seduction.
You're going to put sweats on
and clean, aren't you?
It's going to be so hot.
Okay, bye.
Have fun.
Thanks.
Okay,
here's your ticket.
Thanks. Hey, listen.
I'm never going to lie
to you again, okay?
And I want you to know that
nobody thinks you're stupid.
Thanks, man.
Where you going?
Game's tomorrow
night, Joe.
( door shuts )
Hi.
( greetings all around )
Oh, God.
I'm so glad
you're back.
Wow. So, what
did you guys do?
Oh, you know,
we just drank some beer.
Mike played with the boundaries
of normal social conduct.
( sheepish chuckle )
It's true, I did.
Well, good-bye.
Okay.
Bye.
That was fun,
Pheebs.
I know,
that was fun.
See you, guys.
Rachel,
lock the door.
Lock the door, seriously.
Oh, shoot, I forgot
to pay Phoebe for the drinks.
Wait, wait.
Sorry.
Did he call?
Did that guy call?
No, just his mom.
Oh. Around 8:30?
Yeah.
Then again at 9:00?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, sure.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Uh, no,
she's not here right now.
Can I take a message?
"Bill from the bar."
Okay, Bill from the bar
I'll make sure
she gets your number.
( door opens )
Ah.
So, uh, so, how was it?
Uh, did you guys have
a good time?
Oh, we had so much fun.
It felt so good
to be out.
Uh, Rach?
Yeah?
Never mind.
Hey, you guys.
Hey.
I'll be right back.
I got to go to the bathroom.
Stout. That's a kind of beer.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org